const STORE1 = [
    {
      question: "Which schools does Harry Potter get accepted to in book 1?",
      answers: [
        'Smeltings and Hogwarts',
        'Stonewall High and Hogwarts',
        'Weatherby and Hogwarts',
        'Eton and Hogwarts'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Stonewall High and Hogwarts',
    },
    {
      question: "Who is head of Gryffindor House while Harry attends Hogwarts?",
      answers: [
        'Godric Gryffindor',
        'Albus Dumbledore',
        'Minerva McGonagall',
        'Rubeus Hagrid'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Minerva McGonagall',
    },
];

const STORE = [
    {
      question: "Which schools does Harry Potter get accepted to in book 1?",
      answers: [
        'Smeltings and Hogwarts',
        'Stonewall High and Hogwarts',
        'Weatherby and Hogwarts',
        'Eton and Hogwarts'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Stonewall High and Hogwarts',
    },
    {
      question: "Who is head of Gryffindor House while Harry attends Hogwarts?",
      answers: [
        'Godric Gryffindor',
        'Albus Dumbledore',
        'Minerva McGonagall',
        'Rubeus Hagrid'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Minerva McGonagall',
    },
    {
      question: "Which former Death Eater was the executioner brought to Buckbeak's appeal?",
      answers: [
        'Avery',
        'Nott',
        'MacNair',
        'Dolohov'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'MacNair',
    },
    {
      question: "Ginny gets a pet in Half Blood Prince, what is it and what does she name it?",
      answers: [
        'Owl, Donald',
        'Puffskein, Reginald',
        'Pygmy Puff, Arnold',
        'Niffler, Harold'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Pygmy Puff, Arnold',
    },
    {
      question: "Never tickle a sleeping... what?",
      answers: [
        'Student',
        'Lion',
        'Snake',
        'Dragon'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Dragon',
    },
    {
      question: "Which rare creatures can be found in the Forbidden Forest?",
      answers: [
        'Acromantula, Centaurs, Dementors, Thestrals, Unicorns',
        'Acromantula, Centaurs, Thestrals, Unicorns, Werewolves',
        'Acromantula, Centaurs, Dragons, Thestrals, Unicorns',
        'Acromantula, Dragons, Thestrals, Unicorns'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Acromantula, Dragons, Thestrals, Unicorns',
    },
    {
      question: "Which Order of the Phoenix members is Draco Malfoy related to and how?",
      answers: [
      'Tonks and Sirius, cousins',
      'Sirius and Lupin, nephew',
      'Harry and Sirius, 1st cousins',
      'Sirius and Snape, nephew'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Tonks and Sirius, cousins',
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Voldemort's only uncle?",
      answers: [
        'James Riddle',
        'Marvolo Gaunt',
        'Merope Riddle',
        'Morfin Gaunt'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Morfin Gaunt',
    },
    {
      question: "Why is Mark Evans significant?",
      answers: [
      'Dudley and his gang lost a fight with him',
      'He was on the Gryffindor Quidditch team',
      "Mark Evans is Voldemort's real name",
      'JK Rowling accidentally gave him an important surname even though he was a background character'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'JK Rowling accidentally gave him an important surname even though he was a background character',
    },
    {
      question: "What is Professor Dumbeldore's full name?",
      answers: [
        'Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore',
        'Albus Percival Abeforth Wulfric Dumbledore',
        'Albus Merlin Wulfric Thomas Dumbledore',
        'Albus Dumbledore'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore',
    }
];

